Walter
What do you think of my frogs
Great frogs
They are quite huge
I have never seen
such massive forest frogs
Definitely better than Lewes's
Daniel
How did you raise these frogs
Did you feed them magic pills
I really owe it all to
Jason's secret feed
for making my frogs grow so well
Daniel just has a good eye for talent
Lewes was being stingy
refused to give me a raise
and looked down on me
Daniel paid top money to hire me
I swore right then
to raise Daniel's frogs to perfection
and beat Lewes's frogs
Walter
something is wrong with these frogs
You better stay away from them
What do you mean
These frogs look fine to me
Cut the crap Lewes
You're just jealous
Jealousy won't get you anywhere
Our frogs are just better than yours
Ignore him Walter
Let's go take a look inside
The ones inside are even bigger
I'm warning you
don't get too close to these frogs
Stop trying to spook us
What's so scary about forest frogs
It's not like they'll bite
What's going on
It's just an accident
It shows the frogs are energetic
and healthy
What is that
A monster
How did this happen
Stay away
Help